

Profile

Business Managament graduate with experience in freelancing projects and personal small scale business management. Confident leader and enthusiastic communicator. Avid learner in technology skills especially interested in data science and renewable resources. Self motivated, therefore, effective at completing tasks with minimal supervision.

Employment History

Medical Brigade Translator, Iglesia de Dios / Compassion

Jun 2017- Jul 2018

I served as a Translator for the Medical Brigade in Fco. Morazán and La Paz of the ONG Compassion.

Team's Leader, Rozen, Tegucigalpa, Honduras

Jun 2020- Present

Leader of the startups' developing team. Rozen is an upcoming startup that focus in the development of affordable atmospheric water generators for vulnerable communities.

Manager, Lu's Bakery, Tegucigalpa, Honduras

Oct 2020- Present

Manager of Lu's Pet Bakery, personal small scale business. Lu's Pet Bakery is an organic bakery that specializes in personalized treats and baking products for pets. Lu's Management involves activities such as accounting, financial forecasting, human resources management and supervising production. Instagram: @lusbakeryhn

Freelancer designer and business analyst, Baker's Shop HN, Tegucigalpa, Honduras

Oct 2020-Dec 2020

Designed the business's logo, banners and digital ads for the launching campaign.

Developed a business plan for the first year of operations with financial forecasting.

Freelancer Business Analyst, Meraki, Tegucigalpa, Honduras

Jan 2020- Oct 2020

Developed a business plan for the implementation of an e-commerce web page for auxiliary businesses.

Developed Wordpress e-commerce website.

Freelancer Business Analyst, Pollos Campesino, Tegucigalpa, Honduras

Jan, 2019- Apr 2019

Designed banners and digital ads for the summer's marketing campaign. Developed a business plan for the restauration of the restaurant's Kennedy Branch in Tegucigalpa.

Education

Bachelor Degree in Business Management at Universidad Catolica de Honduras

2017-2020

GPA 4.0

Details

+504 9997-1916 rinherzun@gmail.com

Skills

Microsoft Office

Proejct Management

Strong Critical Thinking Skills

Excelent Oral and Written Communication Skills

Analytical Thinking Skills

Problem Solving Skills

Interpersonal Communication Skills

Time Management Skills

Wordpress

Digital Advertising

Languages

Spanish; Castillan

English

Interests

Data Science Renewable Ressources Animal Protection Fintech

Secondary Degree in Science and Humanities at Eagle Wings School

2014-2017

GPA 4.0

Extra-curricular Activities

Volunteer, Mestizo y Yo, Tegucigalpa, Honduras

2020-Present

Fundraising for animal rescue projects with my personal business. Constantly, working with other volunteers to take care of rescue animals kept by the organization. Also, fostering animals until they are adopted in responsible families.

Volunteer, Becas 20/20 Honduras, Tegucigalpa, Honduras

2019-Present

Assited in diverse volunteer activities such as fundaraising, reforestation, collecting trash, assiting vulnerable comunities and organizing donation events.

Volunteer, Casa de Noe, Tegucigalpa, Honduras

2017-2018

Assiting in fundraising activities for animal rescue projects.

Volunteer, Independent Animal Rescue, Tegucigalpa, Honduras 2017-Present

Developing projects for animal rescue activities such as fostering, rehabilitation and adoption of rescue animals.